John V. Dowdy, Sr. papers, Inclusive: 1926-1986, undated; Bulk: 1952-1972, undated.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Agencies and Commissions, 1952-1984, undated; 2
  - Executive Offices of the President, State of the Union, 1961-1962 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Executive Offices of the President, State of the Union, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Executive Offices of the President, White House Fellows, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Federal Aviation Agency (FAA), Jacksonville Airport, 1960 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, Jacksonville Airport, 1961-1963 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, Jacksonville Airport, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, Jacksonville Airport, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, Jacksonville Airport, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, Jacksonville Airport, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, Jacksonville Airport, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, Jacksonville Airport, 1969-1972 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - FAA, Publications, 1965 National Airport Plan FY 1966-1970 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1952-1956 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1957-1960 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1961-1962 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1963 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1967 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Federal Communications Commission, Cable TV Correspondence, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Federal Communications Commission, Cable TV Information, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Federal Communications Commission, Fredonia Broadcasting Company, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Federal Communications Commission, National Cable Television Association, Inc. (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Federal Communications Commission, National Cable Television Association, Inc. (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Federal Communications Commission, National Cable Television Association, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1965-1971 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Federal Employment, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Federal Employment, 1971-1972 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Federal Employment Overseas, 1965, 1968-1970 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Federal Employment Summer, 1969-1971 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Federal Highway Administration, 1970-1971 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1963-1971 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Federal Housing Administration, 1958-1967 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Federal Housing Administration, 1968-1972 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Federal Housing Administration, Information, 1960-1969 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Federal Housing Administration, Nursing Homes, 1962 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Federal Housing Administration, Rentals, 1960-1961 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Federal Land Bank, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Federal Maritime Administration, 1963-1971 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Federal National Mortgage, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1954, 1961-1969, undated (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1970-1972 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Federal Power Commission, Publications, Northeast Power Failure November 9 and 10, 1965, 1965 December 6 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Federal Reserve Board, 1966-1970 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Federal Savings & Loan Insurance Corporation, 1962-1964, undated (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1952, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1960-1964 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1965-1969 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1970-1972 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Federal Water Pollution Control Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Folklife Foundation, 1970 June 15 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, 1955, 1963, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Operations Administration, 1955 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - General Accounting Office, 1952-1958 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - General Accounting Office, 1962-1971 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - General Service Administration (GSA), 1953-1959 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - General Service Administration, 1960-1961 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - General Service Administration, 1962, undated (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - General Service Administration, 1963 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - General Service Administration, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - General Service Administration, 1965-1967 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - General Service Administration, 1968-1970 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - General Service Administration (GSA), 1971-1972 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - GSA, Publications, Federal Register, 1972 June 1 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - GSA, Publications, Report to Congress: Potential Savings Available Through Purchasing Rather than Leasing Certain Office Copying Machines, 1964 October (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - GSA, Publications, Report to Congress: Unnecessary Costs Resulting from Failure to Consolidate the Leasing of Intercity Communications Lines of Certain Civil Agencies, 1964 October (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Government Printing Office, 1954-1968 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Government Printing Office, 1969-1972 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Indian Claims Commission, 1953-1964 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), 1952, 1955-1959 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1960-1962 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1963-1965 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1966-1968 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1969-1970 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1971-1972, undated (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - ICC, Missouri-Pacific Railroad Reorganization, 1948, 1950-1952 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - ICC, Missouri-Pacific Railroad Reorganization, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - ICC, Missouri-Pacific Railroad Reorganization, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, 1952-1954, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Land and Facilities Administration, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1952-1963 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Library of Congress, 1959-1963 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Library of Congress, 1964 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Library of Congress, 1965 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Library of Congress, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Library of Congress, 1967 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Library of Congress, 1968-1969 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Library of Congress, 1970-1972 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Library of Congress, Publications, Congressional Files, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - National Advisory Commission on Civil Disorders, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - National Aeronautics & Space Administration (NASA), 1958-1963 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - NASA, 1964-1967 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - NASA, 1968-1972 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - NASA, Publications, Report to Congress: Violation of Statutes Governing Federal Employment and Excess Costs Incurred under a Contract for Technical Writing and Related Services Awarded by the Goddard Space Flight Center, 1964 October (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - National Archives & Records Administration, 1965-1971 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - National Capitol Housing Authority, 1970 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - National Council of Churches, 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - National Foundation on Arts & Humanities, 1967-1972 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - National Guard Bureau, 1965-1968 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - National Institute of Health, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1959-1971 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - NLRB, Publications, A Layman’s Guide to Basic Law Under the NLRB Act, 1964 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - NLRB, Publications, Special Analysis: History & Role of the NLRB, 1965 August 27 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - NLRB, Publications, Jurisdictional Guide, undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - National Mediation Board, 1961-1965 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - National Railroad Passenger Corporation (NRPC), 1970-1971 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - NRPC, Publications, Final Report on Basic National Railroad Passenger System, 1971 January 28 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - National Science Foundation, 1962-1972 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - National Security Agency, 1963 February 9 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - National Wildlife Federation (NWF), 1967, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - NWF, Publications, Ecology: A Wild Idea, 1972 March (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - NWF, Publications, Newsletters, 1965-1966, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Occupation & Safety Health Administration, 1972 May 25 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1964-1971 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - OEO, Community Action Program, 1966-1969 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - OEO, Community Action Program, 1970-1972 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - OEO, Community Action Program Application from Center, Texas (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - OEO, Community Action Program Application from Center, Texas (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - OEO, Community Action Program Application from Tri-County Community Action, Inc., 1968 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - OEO, Community Action Program Maps, 1967-1970 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - OEO, Head Start, 1965-1970, undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - OEO, Head Start Application from Center, Texas, 1967 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - OEO, Head Start Information, 1967, undated (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - OEO, Informational Materials, 1964-1971, undated (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - OEO, Job Corps, 1964-1968, 1971, undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - OEO, Job Corps Information, 1965-1967, undated (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - OEO, Legal Services Program, 1967, 1971, undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - OEO, Newsletters, 1970-1972, undated (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - OEO, Participating Agencies in Texas, 1966 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - OEO, Poverty Program, 1964-1969 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - OEO, Poverty Program Publications, 1965, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - OEO, Press Releases, 1965-1968, 1970, undated (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - OEO, Project FIND, 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - OEO, Publications, Communities in Action, 1966 August-September (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - OEO, Publications, Economic Opportunity Act of 1964 and Amendments, 1964-1966 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - OEO, Publications, Information Center National Program Summary — Fiscal Years 1965-1967, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - OEO, Publications, Office of Economic Opportunity Annual Report — Fiscal Years 1969-1970, undated (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - OEO, Publications, Poverty Program Information as of January 1966, 1967 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - OEO, Publications, President’s War on Poverty Program-A Quick Reference Guide, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - OEO, Publications, War on Poverty Program-A Quick Reference Guide, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - OEO, VISTA, 1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - OEO, VISTA Publications, 1956, 1969, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - OEO, Work Study Program, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - OEO, Youth Camps, 1964-1966 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Office of Emergency Planning, 1965-1966 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Office of Emergency Preparedness, 1970-1971 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Office of Management and Budget, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Peace Corps, 1967-1970 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Peace Corps Information, 1965-1971, undated (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Public Building Administration, 1965, 1971-1972 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Public Housing Administration, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Public Land Law Review Commission, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Railroad Retirement Board, 1953-1962 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Railroad Retirement Board, 1960-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Railroad Retirement Board, 1967-1972 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Rural Areas Development, 1970-1971 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Securities & Exchange Commission, 1964, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Selective Service, 1953-1959 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Selective Service, 1960-1965 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Selective Service (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Selective Service (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Selective Service (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Selective Service (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Selective Service (1 of 3), 1968 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Selective Service (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Selective Service (3 of 3), 1968 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Selective Service (1 of 3), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Selective Service (2 of 3), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Selective Service (3 of 3), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Selective Service, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Selective Service, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Selective Service, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Small Business Administration, 1953-1955 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Small Business Administration, 1956-1959 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Small Business Administration, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Small Business Administration, 1961 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Small Business Administration, 1962-1964 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Small Business Administration, 1965 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Small Business Administration, 1966 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Small Business Administration, 1967 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Small Business Administration, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Small Business Administration, 1969 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Small Business Administration, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Small Business Administration, 1971 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Small Business Administration, 1972 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Small Business Administration, Brochures, 1963-1972 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Small Business Administration, Information, 1963-1971, undated (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Small Business Administration, Publications, U.S. Government Purchasing and Sales Directory, 1968 October (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Smithsonian Institute, 1968-1970 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Supreme Court, 1957, 1959 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Supreme Court, 1961-1964 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Supreme Court, 1965-1969 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Supreme Court, 1970-1972, undated (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Supreme Court Cases, Nos. 11, 37, and 43: Graham v. John Deere, 1965 October (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Supreme Court Cases, No. 38: Rosenblatt v. Baer, 1965 October (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Supreme Court Cases, No. 45: Linn v. Plant Guard Workers, 1965 October (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Supreme Court Cases, No. 55: United States v. Adams, October 1965 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Supreme Court Cases, No. 105: Keyishian v. University of the State of New York, 1966 October (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Supreme Court Editorials from the Indianapolis Star, 1957 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Supreme Court, Publications, The George Washington University Magazine, vol. 3, no. 2, 1969 Summer (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Supreme Court, Publications, Significant Decisions of the Supreme Court 1969-70 Term, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Tariff Commission, 1960-1964 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Tariff Commission, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1961, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - United Nations, 1961-1966, undated (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - United Nations, 1970-1972, undated (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - United Nations, Publications, The Peace Keeping Crisis at the UN by Louis Hakasz, undated (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - United Nations, Publications, VISTA, vol. 6, no. 2, 1970 November/December (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - United Nations, Publications, Wanted: Rules to Guide UN Peace-Keeping Operations of the Future by Marion H. McVitty, undated (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - United Nations, Publications, Meet the Press with US Ambassador to the UN Adlai Stevenson, 1961 September 17 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Board of Parole, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - United States Information Agency, 1955, 1961-1969 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - War Claims Commission, 1953-1956 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Water Resources Council, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Veterans Administration, 1952 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Veterans Administration, 1953 (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Veterans Administration (1 of 2), 1954 (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - Veterans Administration (2 of 2), 1954 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Administration (1 of 2), 1955 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Administration (2 of 2), 1955 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Administration, 1956 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Veterans Administration, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Veterans Administration, 1958 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Veterans Administration, 1959 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Veterans Administration, 1960 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Administration, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Administration, 1962 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Administration, 1963 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Veterans Administration, 1964-1966 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Veterans Administration, 1970 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Veterans Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Veterans Administration, Chaplain Corps, 1965 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Veterans Administration, Hospitals, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Administration, Jobs for Veterans, 1970-1972 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Administration, Publications, Federal Benefits for Veterans and Dependents, 1967, 1969, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- Committees, 1952-1972, undated; 3
  During his twenty years of service, Dowdy took his committee assignments seriously. He served for four years on the Post Office and Civil Service Committee and then sixteen years on the Judiciary Committee and its District of Columbia Sub-committee. He eventually became Chairman of this subcommittee, spearheading an investigation into corruption of urban renewal projects in Washington, DC.
  This section is divided into twenty-one committee subseries. Over half of these materials, however, deal with only four committees: District of Columbia, Education and Labor, Judiciary, and Ways and Means. The arrangement is alphabetical by committee or subcommittee and then chronological within the subseries.
  - Agriculture, 1952-1972, undated; 1
    - Agriculture Act of 1970, 1970-1971 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, 1965-1970 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Cattle, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Cattle Industry, 1953-1963 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, 1955 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1970 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Agricultural Act 1965, 1958-1968 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Agricultural Act 1970 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Agricultural Conservation Program, 1970-1971 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Animal Cruelty, 1967-1969 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Animal Treatment, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Conservation, 1958-1978 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Cotton, 1955-1971 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Economics, undated (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Economics, 1954-1966 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Eggs, 1967-1970 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Farm Bill, 1965, 1970 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Fiscal, 1969-1972 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Food Programs, 1967-1972 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Grain, 1954-1971 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Labor, 1968 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Livestock, 1952-1969 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Lumber, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Meat, 1967-1972 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Metcalf Bill, 1969-1971 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Milk, 1956-1971 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Mink, 1970 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Peanuts, 1950-1969 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Pesticides, 1957-1964 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Pests, 1969-1972 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Poultry, 1965-1972 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Produce, 1956-1972 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Rice, 1962-1971 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Rural Electric, 1970-1972 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Rural Electrification, 1958-1966 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Sugar, 1955-1970 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Texas Farm Bureau, 1955-1964 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Tobacco, 1956-1959 (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Watersheds, Floods, and Droughts, 1952-1964 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Cotton, 1956-1970 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Cotton Acreage Allotments, 1953-1955 (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Cotton Act of 1965 (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - Cotton Bill (Cooley Bill), 1963 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Dairy Farmers, 1955-1964 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Dairy Parity, 1954 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Data and NAR, 1966 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Family Farms, 1955 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Farm Bill (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Farm Bill (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Farm Bill (1 of 3), 1965 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Farm Bill (2 of 3), 1965 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Farm Bill (3 of 3), 1965 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Farm Bill Data, 1965 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Farm Bill Problem, 1958 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Farm Bill Program Agriculture Act of 1956 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Farm Bill Program Agriculture Act of 1957 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Farm Bill Program Agriculture Act of 1961 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Farm Credit, 1955-1959 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Farm Credit Act, 1971 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Farm Credit Administration, 1952-1953 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Farm Labor, 1951-1963 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Farm Labor, 1966, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Farm Program, 1954-1964 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Feed Grain Act, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Feed Grains, 1957-1972 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Feed Grains Bill, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Food and Agriculture Act, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Food Stamps, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Forest Bill, 1960 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Forest Research Program, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Forestry, 1953-1971 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Grain Marketing, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Humane Society, 1957 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Innocent Purchasers of Converted Fungible Goods, 1954-1955 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Meat, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Mink, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Omnibus Farm Bill, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Pesticides, 1965-1971 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Poultry, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Poultry and Egg (Broilers), 1956-1958 (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Poultry and Eggs, 1957-1963 (Box 123, Folder 21)
    - Publications, Outline of Program, 1971 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Publications, Policies and Programs of the Texas Federation of Cooperatives, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Publications, Price and Today’s Markets for U.S. Cotton, 1962 September (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Program of Proposed Research, undated (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Publications, Why All Farmers and Ranchers Should Support the Proposed Farm Credit Legislation, 1952 August (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Rice, 1967 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Rural Electrification, 1967-1968 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Soil Bank Program, 1956-1964 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Sugar Act, 1955, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Sugar Bill, 1962-1964 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Wheat and Feed Grain Act, 1963-1964 (Box 124, Folder 11)